[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone. <br /><br />Click \"Continue\" when you're ready to move on.","rt":8431,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":13000,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</s ub>, you  start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":24711,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":37714,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":6099,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":43815,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":10916,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":54732,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":2915,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":57648,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":102134,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":159783,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":2569,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":162353,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":57125,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":219479,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 2 because 1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":4119,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":223599,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second on e to it.  If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":6927,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":230527,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":2249,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":232777,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":7466,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":240244,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":2120,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":242365,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":57276,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":299643,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":6520,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":306165,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":15106,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":321272,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":2190,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":323463,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is  6 or big ger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":51603,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":375068,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":8894,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":383965,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":9929,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":393895,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":2314,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":396211,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":49811,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":446027,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0 because 3 + 3 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":5558,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":451586,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What  is 1 +< sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":8547,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":460133,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 3 because 1 + 2 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":2040,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":462174,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":32605,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":494781,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 4 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 6 = 4.","rt":1681,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":496464,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":5098,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":501563,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0 because 4 + 2 = 6 and 6 -  6 = 0.","rt":2966,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":504530,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":4557,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":509089,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 2 because 0 + 2 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":1891,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":510981,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the sec ond one  to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["3","2"],"rt":7263,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":518245,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2 because 3 + 5 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":6512,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":524758,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":8077,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":532837,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 because 1 + 4 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":2137,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":534975,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":5217,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":540193,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0 because 5 + 1 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":1642,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":541837,"internal_chunk_id":" 0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":4801,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":546638,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 1 because 1 + 0 = 1 and 1 is less than 6.","rt":1774,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":548414,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result .)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["7","1"],"rt":7790,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":556205,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 1 because 5 + 2 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":2011,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":558217,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":6727,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":564945,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the thing that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>). Similarly, 3 is its own inverse under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":1465,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":566411,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":5810,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":572225,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":3464,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":575690,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":3542,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":579233,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1603,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":580837,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 u nder +<s ub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":4160,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":584999,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1355,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":586355,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":3176,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":589532,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1590,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":591123,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":6329,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":597454,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1818,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":599274,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"Let's review: under +<sub>6</sub>, the inverse of 0 is 0, the inverse of 1 is 5 and the inverse of 5 is 1, the inverse of 2 is 4 and the inverse of 4 is 2, and finally the inverse of 3 is 3. Do you see a relationship between an element and its inverse under +<sub>6</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":4311,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":603586,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation can simply be performed starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":2448,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":606035,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we jus t learne d. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because of this, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br /><br /> However, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":7167,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":613203,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","response_history":["Yes"],"rt":5858,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":619062,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":1800,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":620864,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":4968,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":625833,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 5 is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</ sub> 5,  3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":1721,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":627556,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":3227,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":630784,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but the re is no  way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":1617,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":632405,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","response_history":["Yes"],"rt":5737,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":638143,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":1730,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":639874,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Let's review: under +<sub>6</sub>, 1 and 5 are generators. However, 0, 2, 3, and 4 are not generators. Try playing with these non-gener ators an d seeing which elements each of them does generate (i.e. which elements you can get by combining each non-generator with itself repeatedly). Do you see relationships among particular subsets of the elements that are not generators under +<sub>6</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"anything under 3 2 or 1","response_history":["anything under 3 2 or 1"],"rt":20836,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":660711,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />We'll give you one practice question with feedback to make sure you understand the new operation. After that, try to complete the remaining questions as accurately as possible.","rt":4460,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":665173,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":5326,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":670501,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":1810,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":672313,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":32041,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":704355,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":5456,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":709813,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":4234,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":714049,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":5347,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":719397,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":5877,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":725275,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"5 is under 6 so just leave it","response_history":["5 is under 9","5 is under 6 so just leave it"],"rt":15551,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":740828,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"12 - 6 because its over 6","response_history":["12 - 6 because its over 6"],"rt":9796,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":750626,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"dont remember","response_history":["dont remember"],"rt":102978,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":853615,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":5253,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":858869,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":3692,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":862564,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"6 because - 3","response_history":["6 because - 3"],"rt":9569,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":872134,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"cant remember","response_history":["cant reember","cant ree","cant remember"],"rt":15924,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":888059,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"i think you just remove 3 from 9","response_history":["vsny ","i think you just remove 3 from 9"],"rt":10101,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":898162,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words  how you  got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no because its odd","response_history":["yes.","yes","ye","y","no because its odd"],"rt":7699,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":905862,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"yes beause its even and equals odd","response_history":["yes beause its even and equals odd"],"rt":7646,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":913509,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use \"+_n\", and your ans wers can  include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":383727,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":1297237,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"anything that is a positive number","response_history":["anything that is a positive u","anything that is a positive number"],"rt":18669,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":1315908,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"anything that is positive","response_history":["anything that is positive"],"rt":12636,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":86,"time_elapsed":1328545,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"because if anythign is a positive integer","response_history":["because if anythign is a positive integer"],"rt":470057,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":87,"time_elapsed":1798603,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":6128,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":88,"time_elapsed":1804733,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +< sub>n</s ub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":5188,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":89,"time_elapsed":1809922,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must divide n.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","response_history":["True"],"rt":4818,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":90,"time_elapsed":1814741,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words why your answer is corret.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"True","response":"i dont remember","response_history":["i dont remember"],"rt":611762,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":91,"time_elapsed":2426504,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Always","response_history":["Always"],"rt":4380,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":92,"time_elapsed":2430885,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words why your answer is corret.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"sometimes","response":"positive numbers + 6","response_history":["positive nume","positive numbers + 6"],"rt":482384,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":93,"time_elapsed":2913271,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":" If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Always","response_history":["Always"],"rt":3922,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":94,"time_elapsed":2917203,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background. Please press \"Continue\" to continue.","rt":1719,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":95,"time_elapsed":2918924,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"28","response_history":["28"],"rt":4139,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":96,"time_elapsed":2923065,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"Bachelors Degree","response_history":["Bachelors Degree"],"rt":4143,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":97,"time_elapsed":2927209,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"alegbra 1","response_history":["aleg","alegbra 1"],"rt":6572,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":98,"time_elapsed":2933783,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 -  never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":3849,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":99,"time_elapsed":2937635,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":2657,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":100,"time_elapsed":2940293,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned  somethin g from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":3982,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":101,"time_elapsed":2944276,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - not at all","response_history":["1 - not at all"],"rt":4969,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":102,"time_elapsed":2949246,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - not at all","response_history":["1 - not at all"],"rt":3285,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":103,"time_elapsed":2952533,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Female","response_history":["Female"],"rt":2867,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":104,"time_elapsed":2955401,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"What is/are your native language(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"english","response_history":["english"],"rt":3822,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":105,"time_elapsed":2959225,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no","response_history":["no"],"rt":3652,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":106,"time_elapsed":2962878,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"hard","response_history":["hard"],"rt":3717,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":107,"time_elapsed":2966597,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"}]